Anthony J. Silva Papers WAG.205
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Anthony J. Silva Papers
1912-2001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Silva, Anthony J.
WAG.205
1 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
Scope and Contents
Materials relating to the history of the United Telegraphers Union.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Anthony J. Silva, 2000. The accession number associated with this gift is 2000.009.
Silva, Anthony J.
- Agreements, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreements: American Communications Association (ACA) and Postal Telegraph Company, January 14, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agreements: ACA and Postal Telegraph-Cable Company, October 1, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agreements: Western Union and ACA, Local 40, April 1, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Association Western Union Employees (AWUE): Survey, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Association Western Union Employees (AWUE): Officers List, 1919-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Arbitrations: NLRB and Western Union, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Clippings, 1912-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1919-1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "Dots, Dashes, and Tyranny: Western Union's Company Union Remembered." Silva, Anthony J. Labor's Heritage, Spring/Summer 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Histories, Records of Achievements, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Telegraph World, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Telegraph World, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Telegraph World, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Telegraph World, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Telegraph World, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Telegraph World, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Telegraph World, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Telegraph World, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Telegraph World, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Telegraph World, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Telegraph World, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Telegraph World, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Telegraph World, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Telegraph World, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- United Telegraph Workers, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 14a)
- Western Union News, 1914, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 14a)